<blog>
	<post>
		<date>November 11, 2022</date>
		<author>James Karoly Jr</author>
		<title>Album Review: King Princess - Hold On Baby</title>
		<summary>
			<image_path>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/4/4a/King_Princess_Hold_On_Baby.webp</image_path>
			<text>Released July 29, 2022</text>
		</summary>
		<body>King Princess is the recording name of Mikaela Straus and she just released her second album this past July. The release was preceded by 4 singles. Straus works with a variety of producers including Mark Ronson and Aaron Dessner. Taylor Hawkins, drummer for the Foo Fighters who died in March 2022, plays drums on the closing track "Let Us Die." Aaron Dessner of The National produces two of the best songs on the album: "I Hate Myself, I Want To Party" and "Change the Locks." The album revolves around dealing with depression and relationships in this changing world. The song "Change the Locks" specifically deals with a slump in her relationship during the pandemic. The lyrics throughout the album are largely introspective and questioning. I love albums like this because while the lyrics can be sad, the music behind it is largely upbeat and it is not filled with ballads. Dancing (or Rocking in some songs) to your sadness can be cathartic.</body>
	</post>
	<post>
		<date>November 20, 2022</date>
		<author>James Karoly Jr</author>
		<title>Album Review: Big Thief - Dragon New Warm Mountain I Believe In You</title>
		<summary>
			<image_path>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/4/4d/Dragon_New_Warm_Mountain_I_Believe_in_You_%28Big_Thief%29.png</image_path>
			<text>Released February 11, 2022</text>
		</summary>
		<body>Big Thief is a band consisting of vocalist Adrianne Lenker, guitarist Buck Meek, bass guitarist Max Oleartchik, and dummer James Krivchenia. They released their 5th album in February of 2022. Their previous albums usually consisted of a single style or genre, while this album was envisioned as a way to put all their different styles into one album. The album was recorded in 4 different locations with 4 different engineers, and each session had a specific sonic plan on how they wanted it to sound. While it sounds a little disjointed, it's surprising how cohesive the album can be at points. While I was never a huge fan of the band before, I became easily obsessed with this album when released, even though some of the songs venture into bluegrass/country territory. The lead singers voice is entirely unique, soft and ethereal in some songs, while being deep and dark in others. The music itself is fascinating, and you can tell they enjoyed experimenting in the studio. I love this album because it takes you on a journey. Some of the lyrics are actually funny, and that can be incredibly hard to pull off without sounding cheesy or trying too hard.</body>
	</post>
	<post>
		<date>December 1, 2022</date>
		<author>James Karoly Jr</author>
		<title>Album Review: Haim - Women in Music Pt III</title>
		<summary>
			<image_path>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/6/64/Haim_-_Women_in_Music_Pt._III.png</image_path>
			<text>Released June 26, 2020</text>
		</summary>
		<body>Haim is band consisting of three sisters from Los Angeles, CA. Este, Danielle and Alana Haim have been making music together since 2007 but didn't take the and seriously until 2012. I was a huge fan of their first album, but didn't really connect with their second. When this album came out, I was entranced, and even though it was released in June 2020, I still listen to it almost every week. I think its partly because I was (and still am) a big Fleetwood Mac fan as a kid thanks to my parents, and you can tell they are a big influence on Haim. I am also a huge fan of the producers of the album. Danielle Haim produced along with Rostam Batmanglij (formerly a part of Vampire Weekend) and Ariel Rechtshaid, who has produced for Vampire Weekend, Charli XCX, Adele, Carly Rae Jepsen and Haim's other two albums. I know this album is going to follow me through my life, every time I listen to it, its like the first time all over again. I don't think I could get sick of these songs, although time will tell.  </body>
	</post>
</blog>